apkfileplace.com 2012-11-09

# Privacy Policy | Free Download Android APK Apps and Game

## Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below.

**Cookies**  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our website is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Traffic Reports**  
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**  
We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but we may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**  
If our website is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our website, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.  
**  
Links**  
Our website frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website.

**Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Notification of Changes**  
When our website makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.
